foreign
[Music]
knowledge is power
reality is
[Music]
and
professional like this and you got like
your headset on I know I'm like a pilot
actually
maybe you are uh for some people that's
true yeah in multiple ways actually yeah
pilot is a is a multi-dimensional term
really too because there's like a like
pilot in your oven too as well right to
heat it up and the first episode of
shows a pilot right big flight who's the
driver
oh I love that I'm so excited to be here
yeah I'm so excited to see you um I mean
yeah let's just I mean we'll crank it so
uh you've been on the podcast before so
people can definitely go check out those
um and I also think it's like exciting
to go see just you and me both are
growth I'm sure that we've like expanded
so much since even those episodes you
know like just within the last few years
so like we've been you know throughout
throughout this journey I feel like of
self-exploration and trying to like
serve people and whatever that means to
us and I feel like you and I always
every few months we intertwine and we
have like these intense like
synchronistic moments through Instagram
messages and meeting up and stuff so
yeah it's always beautiful so um I will
definitely include like a bio of yours
so people can kind of get filled in on
who you are and what your background is
and kind of what's what led you here so
assume that is below you
um but otherwise like like how are you
Jay what have you been up to what's
going on thank you so much yeah the
witnessing your girl with those dresses
especially from where we come from so
those of you who don't know us we've
been we've seen each other in it you
know I met Jake at a house party I think
I was like 15. and I remember this like
it was yesterday I can like go back to
that memory and we both actually
connected because our parents were in
recovery are still currently using so we
kind of had that like
we know what it's like to have
parents of substance abuse you know so I
feel like even though we were I was
drinking and quote quote lost I feel
like our connection has always been like
solid you know even before we knew what
solid meant as connections I feel like
in the beginning when he said that
growth is so true because when you live
where we live a lot of people don't get
out of it they don't grow I live where
we live and it's I witness people who
never exit the cement the dandelions
that never sprout in that cement you
know and I feel like for us we are those
dandelions that you see in between those
cracks especially coming from Longview
Kelso area where it's not really
the energy doesn't really
support and nourish growth for thinking
outside the box right they kind of want
us to follow XYZ work at the Mill until
you die this is just the way it is you
know you were there you were at the Mill
weren't you like you kind of were like
yeah and I remember like you've been
making music and I'm like this is your
full-time job like go for it like I've
always seen that in you like the
entrepreneurship and like just the
growth really comes from being an
entrepreneurship like leading that ship
of service which you kind of touched on
and how I'm doing is just being of
service with every single connection I
have that's why the celestian prophecy I
recommend it to you because it's really
crazy that that book is just getting
into your awareness because that book
completely changed my life
um it's a true story but it's all about
being of service and being open to being
of service and what I mean by that
service doesn't mean you have to be in
the service industry right it's actually
checking out at a gas station and
looking them in the eyes and being like
how are you feeling today
that's service like it gives me
goosebumps because
yeah like it's like that to me is being
of service going on here and talking
about being of service like
I've personally I'm in the service
industry you know as a full-time Reiki
practitioner water la la right my job
how I get paid is to be of service but I
also choose to be of service with with
every interaction I have
like I literally and I believe that
everyone that I come in contact with
they have a message for me
truly if you like don't look at what
they're look like get out of like how
people are like presented and like I go
like what does this person have to
actually offer me and the book talks
about that everyone that you meet
there's a message there and when he's in
the keys it's kind of like we're on like
this map like life like right like Ford
life and everyone you meet is like if it
doesn't matter what their role is we
each have you know when you're really in
tune and you're really connected to the
consciousness of Oneness which I am
I realize everyone I'm seeing is myself
so what does myself have to teach myself
you know it's like this constant mirror
this constant like reflection and I've
noticed since I really
honored and accepted the Oneness that I
don't get triggered by people's actions
anymore
yeah I'm like
oh well I mean I feel like when you show
up and you're really here with someone
like you know someone who's you you're
out of capture you know you go to a gas
station a convenience store and and that
person is going through the motions and
they're thinking about their own thing
and everyone's just like yeah hello hey
how are you and it's just no eye contact
and it's just the money exchange
whatever boom boom they don't exchange
energy and then suddenly you get like
someone someone like you or I in there
and we're like how are you really hi and
and they're just uh
you know in in a so so I what's
interesting and I I'm I'm over halfway
through of the uh Celestine process I
mispronouncing it the the book that you
recommended
um is it Celestine process or celestian
tomato yeah yeah whatever
um but yeah no it is the synchronistic
nature of everything involved in that
book is just mind-blowing I've been so
excited to talk to you about it just
because you recommended it in a
synchronistic way because I had this
like amazing conversation the night
before with a co-worker who mentioned it
and um it's just been a while but but so
something that I was talking with that
same co-worker that relates back to this
situation of us going to the convenience
store and kind of being able to pull
someone out of
um their their loops and their cycles of
our uh who we think ourselves to be
when you show up in a situation
from a place of service you're not
thinking about yourself I think the
biggest thing you're blocking
synchronicities when you're thinking
about yourself and that seems like well
what do you mean by that but I think
that you'll notice if you walk around in
life
um and you feel like you're not
connecting with people you're not having
these synchronicities are you thinking
about yourself what is the loot playing
are you feeling sorry for yourself are
you trying to benefit yourself are you
trying to how do I get what I want so I
can be this so I can feel this that
thing that you're trying to feel in the
end if you keep asking yourself these
questions why am I thinking about myself
it's just here it's just being with with
people that you're meeting you're trying
to arrive at a place where you're not
neurotically just constantly thinking
about yourself so the active service I
would love to expand on service Jay
because I have come
um though I I was I think I was
mentioning about it the last like month
or so maybe a little bit longer um I've
actually come back around to like
re-reading some like Christianity type
stuff and listening to like some I'm
coming to an understanding I used to
have such a block about it and I was I
love all this Eastern philosophy and I'm
like that's the way and recently I've
like come full circle to understand
what's what's being said in like
Christian and I feel like service is so
big but I think it's often misunderstood
um yes in a lot of these so yeah I want
to I want to talk a little bit more
about service what do you have to expand
on that yeah it's interesting so I never
grew up religious I've been to church
like a few times I had too many
questions honestly that couldn't be
answered which I know that that's
probably common
um but I'm also not a follower let's
just put that out there and I and
anything I do I feel like I'm always
like trying to just be myself and I felt
that
I feel like when it comes to the
Christian you know this is going to be
triggering for a lot of people who are
quote unquote maybe brainwashed we are
taught that service is to get to
somewhere better after this life and
sometimes with that Christian mindset
they're serving for the afterlife
they're thinking well where am I going
because they have that well if I'm bad
I'm going to hell I'm good and then they
have they have that so when you're
coming a place to be of service from the
idea that you're gonna go somewhere
better after this
you might not be in alignment
do you know what I mean I'm I'm giving
this person ten dollars because Jesus up
there is keeping track of XYZ of my good
deeds
like it's Santa Claus I'm a naughty nice
list or something to me that's not being
of service if you're donating and you're
showing it and you're like I don't hate
it you're that's for yourself
that's not actually to me so I I sat
with that because like what are the
intentions of service and to me
um I know when I sat with Ayahuasca one
of my intentions with the medicine was
uh I get chills talking about it I was
like I'm here to be of service I've
always known that you know I went into
nursing trying to be of service
unfortunately it wasn't in alignment I
don't um agree with a lot of Western
medicine
um I didn't feel of service in that
right so if I don't feel enough service
even though it's a service job I don't
feel like it's in service for me then
I'm doing a disservice well that's
another thing with service to me is
is it actually in alignment with how you
are supposed to serve because we all
serve in different ways some of us are
messengers right like some of us are
literally here to to to speak to spread
messages some people are really here to
wash dogs and that's them being of
service they love animals so much like
so whatever it is like I feel like we
often get caught up and like what am I
here to do what's my purpose
oh we get so caught I've been there in
that Loop like how am I supposed to
serve and it's like ask
ask
literally that's what I did and I mean I
mean Reiki to me is full of service
because I'm just connecting people to
whatever it is up there out there in
there and to me being of service like to
sum it up is really
serving
the Consciousness
to elevate the vibrational frequency of
every single thing I come in contact
with if that's planting a seed in the
garden
it's not always with physical people
that I'm being of service with right
it's feeding the birds at my house right
it's emptying the it's emptying the pond
and putting new water in for the frogs
to grow in healthy water it's cutting
Ivy off a tree
to help that grow because that tree
can't do it itself to me being of
service is fully being lit up
because I'm a light worker
um to me being of service is being
authentic so I can help other people be
authentic by just being me being of
service is also
staying true to myself and the best
thing that you can do if you're
listening to this right I don't even
know what to do is focus on your own
vibration at first be a little selfish
if you need to tell you because you
can't be of service if you don't have
any light with it if you're dimmed oh
sorry go ahead what does that mean focus
on your own vibration what does that
mean okay so focus on your own vibration
so I'm all about
where he is Reiki is
an ancient style Japanese technique for
stress reduction relaxation essentially
I'm channeling the universe through my
body
that sounds insane I know it's still
freaking I still don't get it I but I do
it people come up people show up I'm
like here I am that to me is being of
service but vibrational frequency
everything is vibration everything is
vibration and I look I not me I don't
look I have the inner awareness that
this computer screen this microphone the
tea I'm drinking has a vibration in it
right I mean I'm sure you've seen like
the water the water things when you have
one water it says I hate you a note in
it and the other water says I love you
that water that says I hate you molds
doesn't grow the other water grows just
with a piece of paper with words on it
so vibration to me is and keeping your
vibration in alignment and high is
that's your personal responsibility
until you can master that or at least
have some awareness of that it's hard to
serve other people because you're you're
doing a disservice to your own frequency
once you can tap into your own vibration
what I mean by your own vibration is
what are your thoughts
if it's constantly negative it's really
hard to even hear how you can be of
service like you're kind of mentioning
how if you're looping around in that
neurotic like me me me me me me it's
really hard to be of service for me I
don't know how to describe it it was
just like
I just am of service like it's like it's
like this something happens where you
just shift into it like you said like
you don't even know it's happening
sometimes
like it really does just shift into it
and to me about my vibration is
just being pure hearted really coming
from the heart space
and whatever that looks like for you if
there's some wounds in there if there's
some hurt in there it's gonna be also
hard to open up because being of service
means that whatever you connect with
shoots through your body
um my inner voice like talk to that
person I don't want it well I'm
embarrassed I don't give up like go talk
to that person yeah what is that why is
there that thing saying go talk to that
person like why is there that little
feeling you know in in the different
times in our lives we're a little more
in tune little less in tune I think we
can all resonate with some sort of like
yeah I feel like this this sort of thing
and I feel like things are acting in my
favor
um and I feel like I'm meeting these
people whatever and then you know maybe
go through some times where you don't
have any of that and and you're like
what's going on and life seems a little
little maybe gray or um something I
think you could like look back and go oh
I was I was thinking about myself or
maybe I was caught in my story again
something really amazing that I love in
this The Celestine prophecies so
whatever
um uh is the um like there's this
emphasis subtly it inadvertently kind of
like they painted beautifully on healing
our childhood trauma okay and um but I I
really loved the expansion of it I love
hearing every different view of this
like I was just talking with some
friends the other day
um and I found myself trying to explain
childhood trauma and I was going to like
Gabor mate and um a couple of these
intellectuals that like have written
these books on trauma but but I found
myself wanting to really expand the
definition of look it it doesn't mean
that you were just like you know when
you were a defenseless child an adult
you know physically harmed you or or an
adult sexually assaulted you or you were
neglected or your parents had to work
all the time and you never saw them and
you had to raise your sisters or
whatever it is you know essentially
there is a pattern a belief system
um that you were taught to survive like
you you learned this is how humans learn
how to survive and adapt and belong in
the world okay so if I in order to get
love which is part of our being we want
to feel love it's part of what moves us
forward is what moves us forward we find
these we're pattern seeking machines so
we see our parents we're like oh okay
well I did this I said this that didn't
give me love I did this I said this that
got me love okay you have this pattern
and it will follow you through your
whole life in the huge the huge thing is
is that I was trying to expand with my
friends was kind of like
we we all have childhood trauma let's
say that everyone has something from
their childhood some structure
that could use unwinding that could use
a second look because it might be
blocking you it might be the reason why
you're neurotically looping and you
can't talk to these people at the
convenience store
um so so it's it's so I don't know I
think um childhood trauma seems like
this closed door to so many people
because they're like whoa like you know
it seemed like my life was was okay like
my parents loved me
um you know I still I'm still friends
with my pair I'm talking to my parents
so like I don't really want to go around
saying I have childhood trauma and and I
just want to invite those people you
know like
don't don't wall this off you know these
these terms like childhood trauma
they're it's it's not there's no
gatekeeping here it's essentially as
humans we're discovering and we're using
different words and maybe some people
have more severity than others or
whatever but the worst thing you've ever
been through is the worst thing you've
ever been through so you
can learn at whatever age as an adult
you can look back and go huh maybe I'm
not in alignment or maybe there's things
that are no longer serving me that I
that I can unwind so and that's part
part of the process like so I think
things like um you know people like you
and I seem to be helping people
understand and teach these things within
themselves
um so so what what does that does that
resonate with you Jay um this thought of
childhood trauma yeah and you know even
deeper than that you want to get into
DNA and ancestral trauma the wounds you
know when you're in your mom's womb you
got your grandma's eggs on you
that science you might not have trauma
did your mom
did your did your grandma have trauma I
mean I think all of America and all of
this world can say yeah it was pretty
tough back then
that's in US
do you know what I mean so yeah
childhood trauma if you're like oh my
like how he you know you're saying like
oh my life was good
getting yelled at in preschool is trauma
like it doesn't always have to be from
parents it can be from outside stuff
like feeling left out feeling neglected
right all of those wait like you're
mentioning like there's so many ways it
comes up and it shows up and as someone
who again does energy work I've never
had anyone on my table that I haven't
cleared or felt some sort of childhood
trauma I've done over hundreds of
sessions
and it might not always be in this life
and those of you who maybe don't are new
to that like I believe I I know I've
lived thousands of if not hundreds of
thousands of lives and the DNA is a
staircase
everyone that's walked before us is
walking in our DNA right now
you know I'm someone who focuses a lot
on ancestral clearing ancestral healing
I do sweat once a month I call in a
different ancestor and I clear that
trauma okay on to the next
we have seven generations behind us
minimum and seven before us so something
else of being of service is I don't have
children yet if I I don't know I haven't
decided yet
um I'm working for Seven Generations
before me you know I have a lot of
people coming to you I don't know if I'm
a good mom if I'm like are you being a
better mom than how you were raised yes
then you're doing it so that's just a
tip for the moms out there like my
trauma I'm causing trauma if you're
doing better than your mom you're doing
it right easy on yourself be easy yeah
you're doing okay yeah but the trauma
thing yeah it it's um the pattern and I
like how you mentioned like patterns and
Cycles because one of my gifts is I have
the ability to actually recognize when
people are in a cycle in a pattern
really easily
like looping like it's almost like I can
see especially if the chakras are wheels
right so I can see where the stories are
circulating at and I can actually
pinpoint what chakra that story is
sitting in and I can actually pinpoint
how that story activates this and
activates that and how when we're
constantly talking about our trauma too
like personally I used to do this like
talk talk talk talk therapy yeah yeah
yeah but sometimes
like let's just get it out of the body
like I mean for real and you're like how
do I do that go lay in the forest go
scream right go to go find energy work
go to meditation go to DNA stuff look at
what you're eating like a lot of times I
find that people don't get better one
because I don't look for the help but
two because I don't even know that that
trauma is sitting in there
like looping like looping looping
looping around like especially women in
the womb
if you had a traumatic birth like
there's so many ways that trauma shows
up and it affects what I was going back
to in the beginning is your vibration
that trauma is secondary to a feeling so
sometimes like you said we're pattern
Seekers I really like that because we
are but we're also if you are sensitive
and you're empathetic empath meaning you
can feel stuff if you feel someone else
has trauma in their body and you're an
empath and you don't know how to protect
yourself you're transferring that into
your body and then you're like oh my God
what's going on I don't feel good that
person like we can go into like how to
protect your energy because I know
personally I used to just
suck everyone's trauma out of their body
for them and then go home and transmute
it like this started happening when I
was a child I know I've been I was
depressed most of my life but looking
back I'm like probably was I was just
not even yours exactly yes
I was like that girl at the party that's
like having those like deep
conversations with someone I just met
and I'm listening and like people are
crying like you know like have you ever
met someone you're like wow I feel so
comfortable I want to tell you my whole
life I'm the person on the other side
yeah I've actually always had that and
when we're like that and if you're like
that and you're listening it's because
one we've been through a lot but two
because we can actually hold genuine
space and three our energetic design is
actually it's a type of energy it's
called a transmuter so every soul
everybody has different energetic gifts
I believe everyone's psychic I believe
everyone has sensitivities we all are
different some are blocked right gene
expression yada yada I can go deep into
that but some of us have the role of
being a transmuter so Jake and I are
transmuters and what I mean by that is
we have this innate gift whether we are
aware of it or not where people are
actually talking to us trauma because
one the soul has an inner awareness that
our soul can [__] process it right
yeah so as our job is to one Listen Hold
space but three not take it on I think
of it as like a like a
like a filtration system for the for the
and that's another way I serve I I
listen and I filter it and then it's
gone
it's a talk about it let's get it out
it's done
get out of the DNA when I sat with
Ayahuasca I saw all my DNA like a
freaking movie
and she's like cut
cut this out cut that out cut this out
oh yeah this happened when you were
three it's still messing you up cut it
out like the in the way DNA replicates
right it just it's four letters our DNA
is made up of four freaking letters it's
three blocks codons
the way it replicates a protein goes on
top of a DNA it rips it in half and it
just
slides across but if you cut the trauma
out DNA cellular healing the trauma
won't get recreated it won't be in the
DNA so what I was seeing on an energetic
level and something else that I
recommend is DNA cellular healing
epigenetics it's finally getting caught
up that our DNA changes with our
environment yep
is
epigenetics is like amazing and I'm so
excited for the future of epigenetics
and also just what it what is here now I
actually have had profound
understandings in um uh um
I feel I got into like a few years ago I
got into epigenetics this guy uh there's
Joe dispenza Greg Braden and Bruce
Lipton Bruce Lipton is a genetic guy
yeah I don't know if you've read any of
his Jay but um yeah he he really changed
my perspective on epgenetic because I I
I think we grow up thinking that there's
things like hereditary or genetics or um
you hear everybody say it like they're I
I was man I have this example
um I was working with these people I was
basically working with this this older
gentleman and his son who was uh like
2021 was working with us as well and uh
the way that I perceive people's
interactions I don't get into their
business unless I'm invited in so I
didn't say anything to these people mind
you but um the the most clear 100
clearest day display of like a trauma
the way that his dad was talking down to
him the way that he was condescending
him the way that the young child would
interact and then I would hear these
conversations like he would jump he'd
like jumped down off the stage and then
said something about his knee and
arthritis and his dad goes yep you're
gonna have arthritis just like me like
there was just this exchange between
these two and I'm from the outside going
oh no stop saying
like hell yeah
there was I almost had to resist the
temptation I actually had to like
because I started to feel a little bit
of um I don't know if I was maybe taking
on the energy or something I started
feeling like a little bit anger like
this guy like he needs to not talk to
someone like that let alone his son like
he's harming his son and he doesn't know
you know I kept my mouth shut was it
this wasn't a situation where I was
invited to an interject
but I think that we get so caught up
with these stories of hereditary
genetics we forget about genetic
expression we forget this a lot of who
we are is learned by like I was saying
ages zero to seven you're watching the
people around you oh I don't get love
from this here's how I get this I get
approval from this when I cry I get this
when I don't cry I get this and we will
go about our life like that and we call
that hereditary often we call that
we don't see it as something we have
control over unwinding
um and I think that yeah epigenetic
expression like what strands of your DNA
are you activating yeah and are you
accepting that okay well my dad said
this and so that's that's truth you're
turning it on yeah yeah like what what
genes are you turning on isn't that an
incredible thing to think that we have
power over that I mean what a what a
terrifying thing at the same time like a
lot of people might hear that and go
whoa I don't want that like wait so what
I what I think about and what I learn is
is my responsibility and it's like yeah
yeah in a sense you can you know oh my
gosh yeah that just brings me back to
that story I told you about it's just
kind of deep this is woo-woo as it gets
but
when
um it's all about DNA though so I love
all that and even the word unwinding you
know in second second before I forget I
maybe you were witnessing that
experience because maybe that's how your
dad treated you and you were witnessing
that and you were healing that moment
within yourself and you didn't realize
it and that anger you felt is that inner
child witnessing
that and someone else
oh that's something worth oh I I'm gonna
sit with that I like that
came through yeah see maybe I was yeah
oh wow okay interesting yeah okay yeah
sorry
that's what I saw when I was seeing so
many people tell me stories I actually
can go to that event and witness it from
a higher point I don't know if that
makes sense met a perspective yeah is
that what it's called yeah cool so yeah
yeah that's right that's what I call it
but yeah
um so uh seven years ago like my
Awakening happened Kundalini
um I'm in Pal's book and this book flies
off the shelf like I'm not kidding like
literally flies off the shelf I'm like
okay this book I'm gonna buy it's called
we the arcterians I'm like oh okay it
was like 500 pages I'm like I meant I go
back home nursing school at this time so
I'm in Tri-Cities and I'm in my bed
and I'm reading this book but I don't
even want to say I'm reading it I'm like
absorbing it
like I've never read a book before like
that like it was like
like 500 pages I like I just
and it's what the book is it's a it's a
direct channeling from arterians
arterians are believed to be on the 5D
but spaceship they're in our Sky you can
see them it's one of the brightest star
constellations arcturians or anyway and
the book is channeling from them from a
lady in New Mexico and so it's all the
art so it's written from arterians think
of it like that whether you resonate or
not those of you but it's pretty much an
arcturian is writing this book
everything that was in there was so true
for me they're explaining how arterius
is they're explaining how they are
they're explaining how they are with
procreation they're explaining like the
vibration they're talking about healing
they're talking about sound they're
talking about how they do school like
so many things that they talk about like
that their species is about is how I've
always felt because when I when I'm on
earth like I'm not gonna lie to you guys
I look around and I'm like I don't
understand sometimes why I'm here I know
why I'm here but sometimes I'm like I
know I'm not from here so I really do
resonate with being a starseed we can
dive into that too but anyway I'm
reading this whole book it's like 500
pages on a game
after I read it it's probably like 3 A.M
right when all the beautiful things
happen in life and I like go into a
trance I'm not trying to I'm not like
meditating like it was just like
and I could tell I was like Lucid or
acid acid asteroid kind of pre I don't
know how to describe it I was aware that
I wasn't sleeping or awake it's kind of
like we know when you can't move your
body but it's not like sleep paralysis
scary it's just like you're in that like
kind of like in between and this fit
yeah yeah yeah and this this figure
comes to me blue like arctarians have
blue skin
and he's just like in my awareness like
floating in front of me but it's like
more like a vibrating like it's not like
I see like an alien being like in my
house with like a spaceship even though
lights were kind of going off but it was
just like this like figure out
silhouette thing and I was like kind of
like vibrating like light because if
you're from 5D it's just light
vibrations it's not always like aliens
are coming it's like no it's a frequency
and he's like vibrating with me
and he he shows me my DNA the reason I'm
bringing sucks this is about DNA he's
showing me my DNA which you guys know
it's double helix spiral strand so it's
they can't see me doing that but it's
spiraled right and the way DNA gets
replicated is it actually rips apart
right and then it copies what's there so
he was literally I was seeing my DNA get
ripped apart
by this being and he was replacing it
with gold
Golden Light
and he would to me and after the and
then the next morning I look on my
mirror which my mirror was facing my bed
which you should not have your mirrors
facing your bed by the way it's a portal
but anyway I didn't know that at the
time and on my mirror and I can post
this picture the left hand corner which
is crazy because the day before I
cleaned my mirror and I lived alone at
this time there was like three like
fingerprints
but they weren't mine it was like and
then above it there was like above it
but they weren't and it was kind of like
triangle shaped so it was like kind of
like human print and then above right
above those was like triangle shaped
fingerprints I put my fingers next to it
those things were way bigger so I was
like
they and to me that means yeah we were
here what you saw wasn't like all
woo-woo in your meditative State like
that was here just in case you woke up
today and wanted to forget about that
you know like no no dude it kind of put
me into a psychosis and like it might be
my wake up my Awakening wasn't gentle
you guys like my Awakening was like uh
my Kundalini woke oh my gosh my
Kundalini like
was self-inflicted I didn't do it on
purpose it just and I like was in
nursing school at this time I was taking
a lot of Adderall like I was like live
by myself like just nursing school
textbooks like super textbooky nursy
like am I Awakening happened and then I
was like I am in a simulation like my
Awakening was harsh I'm like I'm in a
simulation none of this is real what am
I doing here like I was never suicidal
but I was like jump off a bridge what's
gonna happen like I got to those
intrusive thoughts of like is this real
like am I real I'd look in the mirror
I'm like who is this after my Kundalini
Awakening like I didn't recognize who
was in the mirror and it scared I don't
want to say it scared me but it put me
into kind of like a really
alone headspace because I was still
going in nursing school I was showing up
like but no one knew what was going on I
was spending all my time alone I was
either in class studying or at my house
like meditating like I just started to
be upset I quit eating meat I just
started running I started doing a sauna
I was reading and I just started to
meditate constantly
like it just started to organically
happen and I just felt like I was in a
dream
like it just started to happen so after
the DNA thing and all that sort of stuff
happening I started to
remember past lives being on these other
planets and I started to really tap into
like
well I'm not supposed to be a nurse I
kept doing it anyway because I was
already in that program yada yada but I
knew I wasn't going to be a nurse that
long I knew and I know to this day it
sounds really insane to the outside
looking in but I'm here to to speak to
people to awaken DNA and to bring
awareness of who you really are at the
core everyone has Stardust DNA we're all
Cosmic I mean come on
like we come into a freaking womb yeah
follow the umbilical cord and keep
following it
you know like it's not that far-fetched
to to be incarnated on other planets
like Earth isn't that old
to me anyway and so when I realized I'm
like okay like I have lived on other
planets like that's real like I remember
like when I was younger I would just lay
I slept outside like that was my safe
space my home wasn't safe so I slept
outside a lot and I would just stare at
the stars and I'm like
I'm ready to go back like I remember
being little like saying that to the
Stars like so those of you who ever are
if you are a starseed and you don't know
that yet and you don't feel like you fit
in just find your tribe find other
people that you connect with because
that's how I felt at home was I started
to actually meet other star seeds I
started to meet other people who never
felt like Earth was home and never
wanted to be here and it felt homesick
how can you feel homesick from a place
you don't even remember it's that inner
longing of home that we don't even know
and remember that we have
a tangent but no no it's beautiful and I
actually want to talk more about your
Awakening experience I actually just a
couple days ago recorded like sat down
hit record and said
I had a spiritual awakening four to five
years ago here's what happened and I'm
gonna try to tell you about it without
using words like God and whatnot and it
was like it is it was difficult to watch
I think I want to try to get him maybe
it was just a rough draft but um uh but
but uh yeah yeah the The Awakening
experience I it's interesting you you
talked about like you know so I think
there's this innate part of you that
knows like okay I'm a Healer I want to
help people like that seems like without
even intellectualizing that's just like
you're almost working from I have this
feeling that is the capital T truth I'm
trying to catch my intellect up to it
where do I look we look around in our
society says be a nurse be a doctor you
can heal that's the way you heal when
you have a I'm a Healer and our society
has an answer intellectually of well we
have this system set up for you it's
called being a nurse and I think that
yeah like that's part of your Awakening
too of going into it and and going you
know ramdas
um he he was a a psychologist at uh was
it Stanford Harvard whatever um and he
he talks about so elegantly where he's
at this place he's at these like he's
got
yeah
like he's looking around he's like he's
like surely somebody has it all figured
out like you know you keep doing these
courses you you do these psychology
degrees he's meeting with these other
psychologists he's he says um he's like
I have a nice BMW I have a nice house
he's like I have my pilot's license he's
like supposed to know it all and somehow
he's basically described he's looking
around and like somehow still nobody
knows like they don't know it like
they're we're all just playing this game
of being a psychologist and Rhonda
started to become aware of that you know
and then I think that's you know his
path soon led into he met up with
Timothy Leary and they tried
psychedelics and he lost his not only
his body in that s in that experience of
taking mushrooms but he also lost his
identity he lost
um being a psychologist being a
professor
um and he had to what is there left you
know and he had he had to sit in that
and that's like kind of been his path
path to God but um yeah so I think that
um you know everything that happens to
us is so it's so intertwined it's so
interconnected and sometimes it doesn't
feel like it when you're going through
it sometimes it's like like even now if
someone's sitting here trying to think
of their traumas going oh that was
supposed to happen to me yeah are you
sure it's like I'm sorry yeah you chose
it yeah
you chose that that's dude and I love I
have loved coming to an understanding of
that as well um uh Karma and
reincarnation took me a long time to
wrap my head around to wrap them well it
took me a long time to get my head out
of the way
um uh because there is this okay so
listener contemplate this even just like
not even me trying to tell you this is
this is how it is but just contemplate a
what if
what if before
what if before you came here
you had a conversation with everyone in
your life with your parents with
everything you said hey
look I want Spiritual Development just
like you this is our purpose
what's going to give me that and you
shake hands with your parents as Souls
and they say all right I'm gonna do that
and you're gonna do that and you say all
right fist pump boom you shot into
you're born you you know you come out
and there's light and you're at the
hospital and uh and that and you've just
gone through the veil of forgetting as
some call it you know
um and and you don't remember any of
that handshake but now your your task is
Spiritual Development your your
reincarnation here is
to have trauma and quarrels and um
things happen with your parents with
your family with the people that you
interact with with your life with your
Society with your city with your state
with your with your world and your job
is to somehow stay above water to
navigate and like try and be clear-eyed
and understand it so you can now help
other people who have the same handshake
afterwards
um uh I guess that was a bit of a change
I'm not sure what I was circling but I
love that yeah and I actually actually
have a reincarnation story personal one
that's trippy as yeah yeah all of that
so those of you again reincarnation if
that's new for you like I'm just about
to just
so
um I was like three years old and I'm
going up to my grandma my dad's mom who
her and I had like a really good
connection like from birth when I was
born she saw angels around me like she
we just have a really tight knit
connection and I'm three years old I'm
at her house I'm like popping around
and I like go up to her and I like tap
her stomach and she's like what I said
remember when I was in your belly and
she's like no you're in your mom's belly
and I'm like yeah before that and I'm
three okay she's like I'm like before
that and she's like no honey you've only
been in your mom's belly like your mom
and I'm like forget it well my Grandma
had a baby die of SIDS and her name was
Jamie
and that baby died at four months old
June 6th
name j-a-y-m-e why do people call me Jay
my name is Jordan Nell
so
yeah
interesting the connected nature like so
it could literally be an agreement that
you had like
and I chose and I chose my mom so my mom
and dad like
they had sex like not that much and I
actually remember going in to my mom's
womb
wow like I actually have that I had that
awareness of
um going within and I actually remember
I've done so much like
um healing with within the womb because
like something else about trauma is
oh the waters you were birthed in like
the Waters of the womb what words were
around you when you were in your mom's
womb so for me personally no one knew I
was in there for seven months
I was grown and hiding
I think 11 months and they did she
didn't know if she was pregnant no my
mom was 16 and she just avoided it and
the first thing when she did tell
someone the first thing was go get an
abortion so the first thing upon finding
out I'm in there and yeah my mom goes
into the clinic and they tell her you
know you have a week to decide and she's
and I remember that I've gone back in
meditation and I actually remember being
in her womb in the clinic with her and
she said she's in the clinic and she
said that she just felt this like no I
can't I can't do that again if you've
had an abortion like there's no judgment
this is just like an experience that my
mom went through and my mom birthed
naturally I was due the date that they
said
um she was about to go to work that day
like my mom worked until she's at Birth
so that's another thing like how our
mothers held US during pregnancy also
affects us
it's not just childhood it's like even
your birth
your birth story affects you right like
you did you get a breastfeed with your
mom right how was your mom's mental
health when you were breastfeeding how
was your mom does she have postpartum I
invite you to ask your moms like how was
your birth did you connect with me right
away my mom didn't connect with me right
away my mom actually you know she
wouldn't be able to say this but my Mom
hated herself so she hated me my dad
left her the day I was born so I was
kind of like that baby in the crib that
just like got pushed hmm so again my mom
and I've done so much healing together
we're like like I said we did Ayahuasca
together to actually heal generational
curses so beautiful like that's so
amazing
D but when you're talking about trauma
and you're talking about like stuff like
that ask your parents like how the birth
was did you want to get conceived right
or were you whoops all that intention
that's why we talk about conscious
conception like so when I do have a
child I plan to be very conscious about
who I'm bringing in the soul that wants
to come through
who is it you're gonna be birthed in
love whatever Soul decides to come into
my womb I've been prepping for but I've
also like when you're being intimate
with your partner and you're trying to
have a child calling in a con a soul is
going through me that trips me ah dude
that's why I haven't had a kid yet I'm
like I'm respond like what yeah
what what greater responsibility to take
on though you know that's why I haven't
because I'm like I'm not there yet
I I wouldn't know I I I I I wouldn't be
so sure about that I mean I I don't know
I I think you I think you'd be in in a
great position
um but I I would like to so I have
actually heard this this Loops right
back around I have actually heard I
can't recall who who somebody on a
podcast talks about they had an
Ayahuasca trip and uh in there like
their purging was so intense and the big
thing that they came out with was
they um it was they had a difficult
birth like when they were birthed into
this world through their mother it was
either umbilical cord wrapped around the
neck
um you know these were they couldn't
breathe right away and that alone had
like traumatized them throughout their
life and they had this this on
everything
yeah yeah they had all these issues and
they never knew they they had no idea
like it wasn't even like a a known thing
in their family like oh yeah you had a
difficult birth you got the umbilical
cord Raptor in your neck I think it was
like something he had to just ReDiscover
but he basically had all these like
mental uh quarrels that were harming him
in his life affecting him from being the
highest version of himself he takes
Ayahuasca and mother Ayahuasca is like
you were traumatized from your birth
canal and uh you know here's how you
deal with it you know whatever and he
was able to expand it and like come
through on the other side and speak
about it so there's just these things
that are underlying the surface that we
may have no we you know we want to put
our intellect around them and try to
here's what happened you know but
there's I mean things you have to really
be open to to to hear them so
um I would love to Jay yeah when you had
told me this uh about a while back ago
you had an experience with Mother
Ayahuasca you traveled across the world
and you did Ayahuasca with your mother
so I would love to I would love to treat
this
um if some someone's tuning in right now
yes if they've never if they've maybe
kind of heard Ayahuasca they're like oh
it's like a psychedelic like some sort
of like you trip out or something can we
start from like someone who really
doesn't know anything about this and and
invite them in and then share whatever
you're willing to share I'm so I'm so
excited to hear about this yeah yeah so
okay Ayahuasca okay so I went to the
Amazon which when I was about 11 12 I'm
like I'm going to the Amazon to do
Ayahuasca so I've always had this innate
yeah this innate connection with
Ayahuasca
um Ayahuasca is considered to be
grandma
of the planet Grandma Spirit
um it's actually a Vine and the way they
found the vine is
they heard it talk to them they actually
found it through mapacho which is father
grandfather which is tobacco so
Ayahuasca and tobacco are married
Union so you actually like smoke a lot
of tobacco when you're with sitting with
Aya because they're together so think
about everything as having a spirit
right plants have spirits think about
just think of it that way and this Vine
like Divine we're connecting to Divine
the tree of life it makes sense that
this medicine is a vine and it's
underground and the vine talked to these
people and said hey I'm here to heal the
world essentially
this is what you do because you can't
just eat the vine like it's not like a
mushroom where you actually pull it up
and you brew it for like 48 Hours like
it's a process like she they really had
to be connected and she gave
instructions for how to do it it's not
like pick the vine eat the vine you're
high yeah there's basically these two
different things that are at different
sides of the Jungle and they they
basically were given guidance to like
hey you have to combine these things
together because our stomach our
microbiome does not process the DMT
without this other part of it itself and
so like even if we just take the Iowa or
the one part of it that we think has the
psychoactive effects it does not affect
our system without this other piece so
yeah super ceremonial like so I did it
in a tribe with the shapibo tribe who
have been in the Amazon since the
beginning they speak shapibo so that's
another thing if you are interested in
Ayahuasca I highly suggest going to the
Amazon because yeah you can do it in the
States but you really want to be
protected
like uh
uh yeah you want to be with shamans let
me just leave it at that so anyway there
I lost this essentially it's you're
actually yeah you're hallucinating but
they actually say that that's a
distraction so if you find yourself like
frying and you're like going on all
these Vision quests that's actually a
distraction you're not actually supposed
to follow that you're actually supposed
to live so in the middle of the trip
um I guess I'll start from the beginning
so you have to go on a dieta so 30 to 60
days before you can even sit with Aya no
marijuana no tobacco no caffeine no meat
no sugar no salt no spices like you got
to be intentional With Your Vessel you
don't have to but at people that didn't
follow the dieta
I could tell because they were not
having a very good experience
um because our vessels are the temple
that the medicine sits in right so
they're going to go in there and kind of
clear it all out so you are in a maloka
and a maloka is just like a term for the
building that we're in
um and there's shamans in the middle so
there's like four shamans particularly
this tribe was a mother a father a son
and the daughter's husband and the son
he started taking Ayahuasca at seven so
these people have been
doing it it's not like again random and
this should people tribe their whole
life is to serve Ayahuasca that's why
they're here they know that at Birth
when you're talking about being of
service like that's their role on this
planet and they're facilitating deep
healing so with Ayahuasca you kind of
set your intentions you know there's um
Maestra and I went to a place called
Arcana which you can look up but she
Christina um Justina like they're
amazing healers
um she sucks bugs out of people it's
insane yeah there's a video on it um and
you
it's dark you fast that whole day so
before actually where I was at before I
did I was like I did combo and combo is
a frog medicine so combo's gonna clean
your blood so it's kind of they take
like an instant type stick and they burn
your skin off and then they put this
frog medicine which is the Venom of a
frog but they do it in a way that's not
harming the Frog and then they actually
put that frog Venom in the burn hole
and what this is you throw up your blood
gets hot is it psychoactive do you have
a trip no DMT no no cycle I did do that
too but this is just more to Clan your
cleanse your blood before we even
receiving Aya so it's a whole prep it's
not like I'm gonna take a bag of
mushrooms today and Fry like it's it's a
it's a
it's definitely something to prep for
but it also brings it up like who are
you without all your addictions who are
you without food who are you without
caffeine who are you without wheat I
used to be a stoner I'm not anymore I
actually don't smoke but um
I so then you do combo you throw up and
again you're throwing up around everyone
like there's no chill here like you have
coolers in front of you and your
projectile vomiting in a room with like
13 other people in the middle of the
Amazon like it's an experience and when
you say with Aya they they smudge you
like Shaman comes in and blows on you
protects you again it's so much about
protection because when you're tapping
into these realms
it's deep it's not like a mushroom trip
it's not like an acid trip like there's
moments of it if you have taken those it
but it's um because it's not supposed to
be like a fried trip
Ayahuasca heals the mind that's the
point she shows you where you're looping
around in Cycles which we're talking
about in the beginning so my first night
so you go on you take a little cup and
you only take like a shot glass
like you don't even need a lot and it is
bitter
it's so I loved it honestly it's earthy
it's bitter and you and they actually
ask you to sit up the whole time if you
can because I guess when you're laying
down you're more susceptible to other
things coming in so if you can keep your
channel sitting upright
and you guys so during this
there's four shamans in the middle and
they're screaming the whole time
so and what they what I mean by
screaming is they're singing because
they're protecting you so they have
songs for the plants so the words that
they're saying is in shapibo but they're
speaking for their their it's songs of
the plant it's Ayahuasca songs are they
harmonizing at all or or if you were to
see from like if you were watching from
the outside of the circle would it sound
a little chaotic or would it sound like
the four of them are working together
because I feel like I've heard before
that it almost sounds like they're like
battling in some senses uh well they're
clearing out demons so they each kind of
have different roles okay so like let's
say someone's having a really bad trip
which happened then it does sound
chaotic because they're clearing them
out because you're supposed to listen to
The Voice so kind of follow one like I
connected with I connected with all of
them but they it's all in harmony
if you're in it because if you can tune
in and you're supposed to listen to them
sing a lot of people don't because
they're in their own head and they're
scared they're not surrendering but I
have a really I can surrender pretty
easily
when you listen to the voices it's
guiding you it's kind of like Alice in
Wonderland like the the work the plans
are guiding you so you're listening to
them and they're singing and it's it's
Ayahuasca talking to you through them
because they take it too they take away
more than us
they take like way more than us so they
are Ayahuasca and they're singing for
and every night was different so I sat
with it four nights the Rhythm and the
the the way it worked was different
every night like the vibe and the
intensity and the electricity
it was different every night because
like the last night I was like one of
the only people who sat with it everyone
was done like they were like I don't
want I'm like I'm ready
because my first few nights people
around me were suffering and it was
actually I told the shamans I'm like
it's hard for me to surrender when
people next to me are suffering and I
feel like I can help so that was a big
lesson for me
was like wow like even though I'm
sitting with Ayahuasca I still have this
awareness of how I can help people
around me like I don't let myself
surrender to my own healing like I'm
always focused about other people so
that was a big lesson for me
um but essentially
you can't you are seeing visions like
everyone experiences different Honestly
though someone next to me he was like
super
I don't know the correct words to say it
but
not a psychopath but psychopath energy
you know how they kind of aren't as
connected like that theory they don't
have souls I'm not saying he was but he
didn't see anything he didn't even feel
the medicine he got he was angry every
night because I would have these
profound he sat next to me eventually he
had to move because I I vibrated him out
because he was mad that I was having
these profound visions and these
experiences and Ayahuasca and I just
like it was like when I drank Ayahuasca
I just felt like oh my gosh like I've
missed her so much like she feels like
my grandma
but if you don't have that
interconnection not saying that this was
like a rare thing but just everyone's
experience was really different
and that's something I want to say too
even though we all took the same
medicine everyone had different
intentions so you tell the shamans your
intentions when you get there
so when you're drinking your cup
you're thinking about your it's so
intentional it's so so intentional and
honestly like for my experience the
first night
um
I for me I got lost in the Visions
because I was seeing like the whole
world
like I was seeing just the suffering I
was seeing the child trafficking I was
seeing
just the suffering on the planet
I was like going deep in that I was
seeing like the Monopoly game board I
was seeing the players I was seeing the
Matrix I was seeing the makers of the
Matrix like I was like I was so profound
and I was like oh my because one of my
goals was to become unplugged fully
energetically from The Matrix those of
you that know the Matrix that's a true
story
um so the first night I was seeing
everything I was seeing the corruption I
was seeing just the slavery the modern
day slave like I was just it was really
like this awareness of like like I was
just seeing it and then I also then I
started to get in my Loops of all the
thought patterns that I usually have and
I was like oh my gosh it's time to exit
so it was like the inner awareness of
like exiting exiting exiting right my
second night was really interesting
um because so I've had an abortion and
then I had a miscarriage and they were
exactly a year apart May 6th and my
abortion story is just crazy because
again aliens came by it came through and
took the baby but yeah that's yeah
there's so much with my life that I'm
like it does not sound real but I'm a
living testimony that this [__] is real
but when I was sitting with ayahuasca
I was like I saw the first baby in my
womb but I saw myself go to the full
term
but I never thought about the baby like
when I had an abortion like it just
wasn't an alignment for me and I never
felt guilty about it maybe because I
didn't process it obviously so I'm
sitting with Ayahuasca and I'm seeing
myself go full term like I'm seeing if I
didn't have the abortion so I'm
literally watching my stomach grow full
term to nine months
and I birth a baby I like pull a baby
out and I'm looking at it and it like
has like a little Hawaiian tank my
partner's Hawaiian and it's a boy and I
[__] you not there's a baby in the room
it's one of the Shaman's babies
okay as soon as I pulled this baby out
of my womb astrally the baby in the room
started to cry for the first time that
night
like and another thing that's really
crazy is that baby would be the same age
as this baby okay sidetracked when I was
pregnant
um the first time I told Dane I said
this baby needs to go to the Amazon
I like I get chills talking about I'm
like we have and when I got pregnant I
was on shrooms whoa yeah no this is
trippy yeah like maybe you were like
wrong door you know yeah like keep going
you know you keep going down the hallway
baby you know like what it was because I
got pregnant on shrooms like it was like
and as soon as I got pregnant as soon as
it happened I was like oh my God I'm
pregnant he was like you don't know that
I'm like I am pregnant I felt like I
think women know that I think I think
that yeah often yeah I mean I'm really
into my body anyway so when I was
pregnant I said Dane I was like I don't
know what it is but I have to go to I'm
like if I if we keep this baby it has to
be born in the Amazon like it was just
this like crazy thought pattern like I
said I am not the right mom for this
baby
like I and I'm not I'm not like I just I
had this like deep thing on me I was
like I'm not the mom for this baby this
baby needs to be in the Amazon
so when I saw that baby
in the Amazon and it just had this like
smile I mean I don't know I have a good
babies love me but when I had that
awareness of
birthing this baby astrally on Ayahuasca
and when I pull it out of my womb the
baby in the room started to cry at the
same time the baby hasn't cried all
night people are screaming you don't
even know the baby's in the room as soon
as I birth the baby as if a newborn came
out the baby in the room started to cry
and I'm like what in the actual to me
like I just I at that point I'm like
what is this life and then I'm like it's
time to purge so I go in the bathroom
and I'm purging and it's it's kind of
graphic sorry but I'm purging up like
baby Parts almost as if when I had the
abortion and the miscarriage not all
energetically the baby didn't come out
wow I was like when I was not literally
baby Parts but what I was seeing in the
toilet was and then I looked around like
on the bathroom and like when you're
walking it was trippy right and I'm like
looking on the bathroom wall and there's
a fat frog which means cleansing and
then this huge moth which means you know
death and rebirth and I'm like okay
that was that was meant to be that was
like really big experience for me
because I was like
I did that confirmed to me that I did
the right thing with the abortion I
don't have to question that choice
um and secondly but this wasn't even I'm
sorry to interrupt this wasn't even
something that you went like I'm going
to the Amazon to deal with this guilt of
abortion you know it wasn't intentional
right like this is just something I had
no idea I guess I have to
remove this block or this or understand
this situation
that was sitting in my my womb still I
had no idea you know so that's another
thing women if you've had a miscarriage
or an abortion and if you haven't looked
at the energy it may still be sitting
there and guilt and shame maybe cycling
around in your room
preventing you from getting pregnant
again or blocking your abundance or
blocking your creativity or blocking
your pleasure and feeling safe to be
pleasured do you have I I don't want to
derail too much uh I want to still talk
about the story but if someone is in
that position and they're not in a
position right at the second to like
travel to the Amazon and go to do
Ayahuasca is there something you can
maybe recommend that how do we you know
women who might be like ah man maybe I
should bring that back up and sit with
that is there anything that you
recommend yeah I would first literally
ask your body so with your body like
well like is is there clearing that
still could take place within my womb
and feel how your body feels and feel
emotions come up and if there is just
YouTube sacral chakra healing put a
healing frequency on super simple
background noise that's going to be the
sacral chakra so anything sacral chakra
healing you don't have to go to Amazon
to clear this let's just I'm just extra
beautiful beautiful no no I love that
though I think that's so great though
because I yeah I would love if someone
is resonating with that
um I think there's not a lot of guidance
or conversations about that within our
culture so I think yeah yeah totally
psycho Shockley shock or healing I'm
with that cool yeah okay Carry On Your
Iowa I'm sorry that's so much but
I mean there's so much right like I'm
gonna write a book because I just saw so
much but
what's crazy again remember my mom's
across the room
and my mom's never taken any
psychedelics my mom went there because
she had cancer and it wasn't genetic so
she's like what caused this
so it's really cool to be in the same
room as my womb the womb space that I'm
healing from it was just really cool but
another part of my journey that was
really prolific is I guess I'll skip to
the last part just because I know we're
short on time the last night of
Ayahuasca again I took the most of
anyone in the room no one else tripped
I'm like ah finally I can let go because
no one else is crying I can do this
and I'm sitting there and
um I see these three agents in my aura
like literal like Matrix type agent like
Mr Smith's
right there's like three of them in my
aura this is graphic again okay
and I'm like oh no I don't want these in
here because remember one of my
intentions was to unplug from The Matrix
fully so I can help other people unplug
so I saw your taxes your money like
student student debt like I was seeing
all these attachments and like you're a
nurse your license like all these like
things that had me still connected that
were deep in my subconscious I literally
took a samurai sword out and I sliced
their heads off I'm not even kidding
like I was like oh yes like yes get out
of my aura and like in my subconscious
like programming me badass I don't wanna
yeah I was like dancing in the blood
like calling moth style like I don't
know if you know her but she's like a
deity I connect with and just like just
felt so liberated like oh my gosh like
oh I just felt free I felt like okay
to to just be a soul without all
attachments of the the matrixly world
and to just be free in that current
moment and to remember that for when I
do feel overwhelmed by money and all
those things and after all that happened
so many other things happen but I'm
sitting there and precursor one of my
biggest fears since I was a child is
getting eaten by an anaconda like just
precursor to this yeah I don't know why
so Anaconda is the spirit of Ayahuasca
so you guys know she shows up as
anacondas an anaconda opens its mouth
this is how my trip ends last night
Anaconda opened its mouth it goes on the
top of my head and it swallows me whole
literally and in that moment the trip
was done and to me that means Ayahuasca
accepted me into her forever and she's
always with me and I'm a walking
vibration and spreading them out like
that was like a sobering like that was
like all right that's the end of your
trip yes that was the end and I knew
that was the end that's how it finished
an anaconda swallowed me whole
and yep that was it
I wish we could talk about death for for
another three hours I think I I I really
want I I would love to talk about I
think maybe we'll do another podcast
we'll just talk about death I think it's
actually something our culture really
needs to talk about
um oh oh my gosh okay so I love so much
no oh wow okay so so incredible okay so
what um uh you know your mother's
journey is her personal Journey so I can
share a little bit about her she's open
to it yeah it was there what was your
journey together did you guys have any
sort of um you know you see each other
from the cross from across the room and
this it's just absolutely Divine space
of Consciousness was there was there
mother child healing was was there
anything between you and your mother in
that situation so honestly I'm the role
of the mother
in this relationship I've always been
someone she comes to advice for but my
mom had a night where it was super scary
for her super dark
you know she had some bad trips and she
was I was talking to her about it and
she was like I don't get it like why why
was this dark and I said
most of your life has been dark she's
like what do you mean I'm like
you use meth for 10 years you're
physically abused we've been homeless
you didn't like
yeah like you you were checked out of
your life for like 10 years getting like
just house to house to house getting
high
you don't remember my childhood you
don't remember your childhood the reason
it's dark is because that's literally
you you've had so much trauma that
you've literally blocked it out I'll
tell her
this is something that's been hard for
me not now but I would tell her memories
of my trauma and my life she goes I
don't remember and I'm like
so is this in my head
yeah
did I make it up no one else remembers
this trauma Okay cool so I'm you know it
kind of frustrating because she doesn't
remember so
but I would say the most profound moment
that I had was actually taking bufo
buffo is a frog five DMT I loved it you
die it puts the chemicals in your brain
that you experience when you die
told medicine it's like the back it's a
different toad than combo and you smoke
it like in a in a little bubbler and
this is like it's not as like it doesn't
last as long and four people kind of go
at once and the main thing is to
surrender and again I'm really good at
surrendering like I don't know I just
I've mastered that skill I shouldn't say
mastered I've
really good at it you have experience
from past lifetimes yeah yeah yeah and
so my mom and I actually actually the
same time like a little different dude
but my mom was
screaming
and when she was screaming it sounded
like my grandma that
tripped me out and I when I'm I took
mine and I was like light language like
I was like attuning myself like these
like Galactic codes and these Galactic
beings were like like I love death like
I'm so comfortable in that realm so
that's what it takes you it takes you to
your body but if you aren't comfortable
with surrendering and letting those ego
die I've gone through a lot of ego
deaths you're gonna fight it my mom was
fighting it like screaming pounding like
literally like wrestling herself she
would not surrender she couldn't let go
and that's why she got cancer
because she has all this in her that she
doesn't even know it's there and it's
just like let me out see me
so if anything I me being able to
surrender and me bringing to her the
awareness of
validating her trauma that she doesn't
even remember was really key for us
because I'm like Mom like if you don't
remember your childhood
it's bad
if you don't remember your adulthood
yeah like where were you for it you know
what you were checked out what were you
doing what you were you protecting
yourself from even seeing the truth of
what was going on the entire time
so that was like something that I was
really really cool for us to I don't say
cool but it was beautiful for her to
experience was
wow maybe Jordan knows what she's
talking about with energy work
maybe she because when I quit nursing it
was a really big deal for my family
actually a lot of people like stopped
liking me because I was like interesting
when I stepped into the role of an
energy worker it's really interesting
like
the transitions of ego for my ego death
actually like I was dead to people when
I quit it was so interesting like I'm
not a person I'm not here anymore now
that I'm not in that role it it actually
reminds me uh just to talk about myself
again you know loop after Loop but uh it
reminds me of when I started this
podcast after my Spiritual Awakening I
did not know that I had a spiritual
awaken I didn't understand what was
happening to me I was just in this state
trying to like find ground and uh you
know looking about like I said like the
first like the first hundred episodes of
of my podcast I could I could say are
like this is like the beginning of my
journey as I was understanding it you
know so like have hope give me a little
Grace but I remember um the beginning
just my numbers like I'd never cared
about the numbers but it is interesting
to watch
at the beginning everyone was listening
to my podcast and then over the course
of a couple months
less and less less and less because they
started I think when they opened my
podcast they're trying to hear Jake the
DJ the cool guy the cool charismatic fun
popular guy and they hear it and they're
like what what who is this who is this
and they don't connect with that because
the person who they thought they were
connecting with had died I mean he is
completely gone and I don't know if I I
didn't really I mean it's taken me up
until more recently to even fully
understand and like you know I've talked
to you about Kundalini Awakening and I
had the same thing I had I had a crudely
Awakening that I didn't ask for I didn't
know it existed I didn't know it was a
thing I accidentally caused it to happen
but also it was exactly what was
supposed to happen right you know um but
uh yeah it is interesting like you you
kind of Disconnect with these people who
are connected with a version of you that
no longer exists and uh it's it's it's
triggering for them but it's also they
they suddenly like they just you just
they lose interest and you're like all
right see you later
um but but it's been it's been this
beautiful like guidance because you know
the numbers will begin to arise again
for people who who need to hear it not
not people who want to reaffirm that
Jake is still cool guy and he's a cool
DJ guy and he's popular but more for
people who um are need to hear what I'm
here to be of service of you know so
um yeah yeah the the part of you that
has to die off that's so okay so what
has been your um I think we're like
pretty close up here on time but what
has been your integration so how long
ago was this and what because with with
a psychedelic trip I I think it's
similar to a psychedelic trip where it's
not like you know the day after you you
do have these profound things but it
really takes from what I hear as months
maybe even years of integration of
understanding okay here's what happened
to me here's what happened to that
moment here's how it connects to my life
when I was a child here's how uh it will
make my actions going forward so what
was the integration process after taking
this Ayahuasca for you yeah so I
December
exactly the 2021 ish yeah
um coming home was interesting because
it was cold right and it's kind of
interesting to come home to my partner
because he was like I'm trying to
explain it to him and trying to like you
know explain that I'm Different you know
but then it'd be like I would have those
moments of still being triggered and
he'd be like well I thought you're
different I'm like oh like me too hey
like okay you know I promise I'm not
gonna do this anymore
um but honestly the integration for my
mom was really hard because she wasn't
living in her alignment for me I already
was kind of living in alignment before I
left so it was really easy for me to to
keep going I was already I already was
on that I was already doing Reiki I was
already like
on alignment so it wasn't as much of a
hard transition for me but watching my
mom like because she didn't know about
child trafficking she didn't know about
this this all the all the the reason I
bring that up is because that's
shattering to people who don't know
about that yet right she didn't know
about all this darkness in the world and
she got super deep into like
conspiracies after so she's like did you
know about this did you know about this
and we lived together she said did you
know this and I said I know all these
things not that I know everything but
I'm like I've already so it was
interesting because I for me it honestly
showed me how much work I've already
done I'm always work in progress
um but it also showed me
how
aligned I am to hold space for people's
healing
because I Ayahuasca was really easy for
me
I could do it every day it wasn't
challenging for me there's moments of
but I I just
I have such a deep trust in conviction
to whatever created us
you know again not that I'm really you
know but I
I don't know when you hit this point in
your life and your journey where you
just kind of quit questioning it and you
just know it
that's kind of what Ayahuasca did for me
it just it just is
I can channel the universe's energy it
just is people keep showing up I get new
clients every day people are calling me
asking me to do this helping them to do
that like it just is it honestly just
brought this inner awareness of like
yeah you're in alignment good job
good job that's kind of what I felt like
yay you're doing it like yeah yeah yeah
like like you already knew but like the
universe said you know you're doing good
keep going you know to Loop it back to
the beginning of what we were talking
about with Christianity I mean you know
in the Bible he talks Jesus is not
acting as Jesus it's God acting through
Jesus yes and that's this thing of
Life can become this series of of
coincidences and knowings without your
mind and understandings without words
um and um
um you know life is painted you know
time itself is actually Unwound in in
these instances of allowing God or
whatever this thing is to move through
you and be through you and and you
become one with God you know
um yeah so oh my gosh I wish we could
talk forever but I to let you go Jay so
um thank you one more thing on that okay
is that one thing to talk about because
because air loved so much that he she
wanted to experience it in flesh
that's that's what I feel about us being
here on 3D
heaven or whatever realm we couldn't
touch there's no sex there's no food
there is no it just was right and there
was no questions there was no mystery it
wasn't fun and that's what I come down
like it's fun to be a human like I don't
know everything how fun is that I don't
actually know I get to eat I get a hug I
get a feel people on the other side
don't have that they don't have touch
like they don't feel that so that's
another reason to have fun like to be
thankful that we do get to experience
that and that whatever it is loves us so
much that we get to actually experience
that love and when you let that love in
it's just it's amazing I mean I think
about like the first time that you fell
in love I mean maybe you didn't even
feel it so much at that moment like I
can I can sit and just really like
Envision the first time that I truly
felt love or like the first time that
someone like told me that they love me
and I truly understood it and felt it
yeah and like I can't even imagine this
it's beyond words it's this gift that
that like wow wow I'm able to experience
that and like there's these Celestial
beings who like know so much but like if
they didn't go through the third density
like they wouldn't be able to experience
that wow what a gift indeed like to to
yeah to to feel love in in flesh form
yeah love is the only thing that's real
the answer it's love yeah thank you so
much
yeah yeah okay we totally have to do
this again um if you would we'll talk
outside of this but um I I would love to
um talk about death with with you I
think we could have a wonderful
conversation around death um it's
something that uh it's been a lot of my
path and again I just thank you you've
always been a space for me to be open
um you've always been you know you came
to my my house in Castle Rock in in a uh
you were like one of the you walked in
you're like wow thank you for for
allowing me into your mind you know you
said something along those lines and it
made me feel very like okay wow I don't
feel so like crazy and nutty you know I
feel it's a scene for who I am you know
and so so I I've I greatly appreciate
everything that you've done within our
friendship and everything that you're
doing for you know the planet in service
of everyone and um so sometimes I get
caught up in a little bit of Daydreams
about the future of seeing like how
powerful you are in in in the the future
the the future is is bright and
beautiful and I think there's a lot of
people who uh will be hearing there's a
lot of ears that will be thankful for
your voice in the future and I know it
to be true
thank you so much for holding space
always holding space in the ways we've
known how and just yeah like not get not
getting those numbers and everything and
I've always told you like this is you
just gotta trust and and believe and
when you're doing it of service it will
touch those you know most great artists
don't even recognize till they're dead
anyway speaking of death you know then
leaving your mark
leaving your mark That's here to help
and Rippling out for Generations you
know
so thank you so much for having me and
all that you do and just showing up and
being of service you know it takes it
takes a special individual to to
actually be of service and to choose
that
to actually choose that right so thank
you it's cool that you ended on that
because uh yeah I've had recent
synchronicities with with choosing and
uh you know
basically like giving myself up to
service of God for whatever that means
you know so I've had those experiences
lately so Jay will be in touch I love
you so much listeners love yourself
please reach out uh check out Jay uh
what does your Instagram handle again uh
Cosmic mermaid please follow Jay on
Instagram she's a wonderful follow she
posts great things every day and she
also has a link tree with a bunch more
things if you're in town you need some
Reiki healing um I think you don't
underestimate Reiki healing and just the
way that you feel when you're with Jay
and the way you feel afterwards so it's
just wonderful love yourself I love you
guys see you later Jay have a good rest
of your day my friend
bye-bye
at what age do we learn to have better
conversations with ourselves
[Music]
knowledge is power reality
is
[Music]